





















Illustrator After Effects

ceros

I am a digital designer driven by creativity and engagement, specializing in web, apps, and social media platforms. I view design as a journey that collaborates with content to enhance experiences through critical design thinking and research — whether in UX/UI or digital visuals. I possess the expertise to skillfully employ prompt engineering and Al tools to elevate designs.

I excel in customizing designs and content to fit various devices, spanning from smartphones and tablets to larger monitors. What distinguishes my work is the unique blend of passion and skill I bring across layouts, graphics, product mapping, wireframing, typography, and color palettes.

# **EDUCATION**

Mar 2017 - Jun 2017 General Assembly (formerly Bitmaker)

Web Development **Program** 

> Web Development Immersive progam

Jan 2001 - Aug 2001 **Birmingham City University** 

# UK exchange design course

> UK exchange program selected by Toronto Metropolitan University to partake in Birmingham 1998 1999 2000 2001 2002

Aug 2000 **UAL: Central Saint Martins** 

### **Experimentational Design Course**

> Experimentational design course using unconventional materials and concepts

2017

Sep 1998 - Apr 2002 Toronto Metropolitan University (formerly Ryerson University)

### B.A.A. - Fashion Design Degree

> Fashion Design, Fashion Marketing, Consumer Product Design, some Graphic Design

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

with earlier experiences on LinkedIn



# Senior Designer, Digital & Multimedia • Borden Ladner Gervais LLP • Jan 2020 - Feb 2024

> Creating concepts, visuals and digital products for <u>BLG</u> and subsidiary legal services <u>BLG Beyond</u>; from designing web pages and apps to social media platform visuals. Balancing quality, speed, accuracy and consistency in delivering brand standards and goals; Acted as BLG Affinity group committee member



### Digital Designer • Blake, Cassels & Graydon LLP • Aug 2017 - Jan 2020

> Creating digital assets for the launch of <u>blakes.com</u>, web pages, client-facing marketing materials, internal communications, social media platform visual, and print materials



### Design Manager, Consumer Products • Thinkway Toys • Apr 2016 - Mar 2017

> Design Manager in licensed consumer products including Lucas Films Ltd. (Star Wars Rogue One), ©Disney/Pixar (Cars 3), and Universal Studios (Despicable Me 3)



### Associate, Online Product Approval • Disney Consumer Products (Disney Canada) • Nov 2013 - Mar 2016

- > Creative associate as part of Disney Canada OPA team on consumer softlines and hardlines products sold across Canada; including stores such as Walmart Canada and Canadian Tire
- > Working as a team in guiding 50+ licensees on 500+ products seasonally including ©Disney/Pixar and Frozen. Managing online product design approval process and meeting with vendors & licensees on communicating design goals and brand guides, to defining brand initiatives

DOLCE & GABBANA

### Associate • Dolce & Gabbana (Milan, Italy) • Feb 2013 - Sept 2013

> Brought 10 years of Canadian design experience abroad and resulted in an opportunity for Dolce & Gabbana in Milan; preparation and assistance on Fall 2013 and Spring 2014 RTW collections; creation of look books